The program makes no changes to the registry nor to any other operating system or user settings.  It does not require a complex installation procedure and does not have an uninstall program.  If it isn't wanted then just delete it, nothing else will be affected.  It was developed under Windows XP so it runs on both home and professional versions, and it has been tested satisfactorily on Windows Vista.  It hasn't been tested on Windows 7 or on earlier versions of Windows but is expected to run on all from Windows 98 as it doesn't make any complex demands on the operating system.

If you have Windows Vista or Windows 7 and encounter any problems, try altering the compatibility mode to Windows XP.

Unzipping file 'Release v0.6.zip' produces a folder named 'Railway', together with a user manual named 'Manual.pdf', a quick start guide named 'Quick start.pdf', and this file 'readme.txt'.

The 'Railway' folder should be moved to the location from where the program is to run, and must be a read/write location - i.e. somewhere on a hard disk (I suggest in the 'Program Files' folder of the main drive), or a memory stick, but not a CDRom.  For convenience, when the folder has been located, open up the folder and add a shortcut on the desktop to the main program file which is named 'railway.exe'.  This can be done by right clicking on the 'railway.exe' file icon in Windows Explorer, selecting 'Send To', then in the submenu selecting 'Desktop (create shortcut)'.  This desktop shortcut information is for Windows XP, other operating systems might be slightly different.  

Existing users should allow files in their existing 'Railway' folder to be replaced with new ones from the new folder.

I recommended printing 'Quick Start.pdf' (4 pages) for reference during the first use of the program.  'Manual.pdf' is the program's help file in a single document which can also be printed if you wish - it's a 39 page document - though it's available anytime during operation of the program via the 'help' menu.

If you don't have a 'pdf' reader please go to http://get.adobe.com/uk/reader/ to download a free copy.

That's it - ready to go - I hope you like the program and find it useful.

Please let me know how you get on with it - good points, bad points and any errors (hopefully few).  I can be contacted at railwayfeedback@googlemail.com

Best regards,

Albert Ball